U.S. President's Commission on Pension Policy Papers 5280
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. President's Commission on Pension Policy Papers
1979-1980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. President's Commission on Pension Policy
5280
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Reports, pamphlets, correspondence, transcripts.
Papers of the U.S. President's Commission on Pension Policy.
5621938
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Social security -- United States; Old age pensions -- United States; Pension trusts -- United States; United States -- Officials and employees -- Pensions; United States. President's Commission on Pension Policy
5621938
- Agendas and Meeting Materials (Box 1)
  - First Public Meeting, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    23 March 1979
  - Study Groups 1, 2, and 3 Presentations and Discussion, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    22 June 1979
  - Study Group 1: Retirement Age Hearing, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    21 August 1979
  - Study Groups 1, 2, and 3 Reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    28 September 1979. Includes part 1 of Panel Discussion of the Future of the Three- Legged Stool
  - Social Security Integration, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    10 October 1979
  - Study Group 2: Disability Issues, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    19 October 1979
  - Study Group 2: Adequate Retirement Income Hearing, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    24 October 1979
  - Study Group 3: Tax Treatment of Pensions Hearing, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    29 November 1979
  - Retirement Income and Coverage of Women and Minorities, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    30 November 1979
  - Ownership and Control Hearing, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    10-11 December 1979
  - Retirement Income Adequacy Hearing, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    11 January 1980
  - Labor Roundtable Discussions, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    04 February 1980
  - Retirement Age and Income Adequacy, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    25 February 1980
  - Study Group 1 Hearing, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    26 February 1980
  - On the Future of the Three-Legged Stool, part 2, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    13 March 1980
  - Universal Private Pension Plan Coverage, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    17 April 1980
  - Study Group 2: Universal Social Security Coverage, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    18 April 1980
  - Study Group 2: Retirement Income Funding and Financial Issues, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    12 June 1980
  - Study Group 2: State/Local Government Roundtable Discussion, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    13 June 1980
  - Pensions and Tax Policy, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    12 September 1980
  - Public Reaction to Universal Private Pension Plan Proposal, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Social Security's Benefit Structure, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    03 October 1980
  - Early Retirement Hearing, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    09 October 1980
  - Pensions and the Economy: European Approaches, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    23 October 1980
  - Full Commission, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    25-26 October 1980
  - Federal Administration of Pension Programs/ERISA Funding Standards, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    14 November 1980
  - Disabilities Issues, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    21 November 1980
  - Vesting and Portability, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    12 December 1980
  - Pensions: An Old-Age Problem (Box 1, Folder 29)
    This is an audio recording on a reel to reel tape.